[♪♪]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[WHIRRING NOISE]
Son of a...
[♪♪]
[CAMERA WHIRRING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
SKYLER: I'm not leaving.
Walt. I'm not leaving.
Oh. my God.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Ah. I can hear your
cell phone ringing!
This is ridiculous. I can't...
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Ah. Uh... What is
going on with you?
I've left you. like.
23 messages.
And? And?
We need to talk
about the car wash.
You know. Skyler. now is
not a good time for me. okay?
Can we talk about this
later? No. okay? We can't.
Why are you doing...?
[GASPS]
Oh. Jesus. What happened?
Nothing. I just
bumped it. That's all.
Okay. I'm... I'm coming in.
Okay.
Exactly what happened?
It's complicated and I
don't wish to discuss it.
It's none of your concern.
Are you in danger?
Walt.
Walt. I need you
to look me in the eye
and tell me right now.
Are you in danger?
You know what?
Let's just say that I have
a hell of a lot more
on my mind right now
than thinking about
buying a damn car wash.
Okay?
So if you could just...
Please.
Okay.
Okay. Then we go to the police.
What? We tell them everything.
That you're a drug dealer
afraid for your safety and
the safety of your family
and you need help.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
What choice is
there? What choice?
If you're in danger.
then it would be...
Wait. wait. stop. stop. Stop.
You keep saying that
word. "Danger." "Danger."
But you said... No. I
have never used that word.
I said "complicated." and
then you flew off the handle.
Yeah. I flew off the
handle when I saw that.
Okay? Where'd
that come from? Hm?
A fall in the shower? Uh...
This is just so
passive-aggressive. you know.
Passive-aggressive?
I go two days without returning
your phone calls. two days.
and I have one
minor little incident.
and now you're telling me
that I should turn
myself in to the police!
A minor incident? Yes.
What minor little incident?
I had an argument
with a co-worker. okay?
And?
I had an argument.
We were in this bar
and we were discussing a
particular business strategy.
And it got heated and out of
control. and he hit me. Once.
And I didn't retaliate because
he's a much older man.
And that's it.
You were in a bar fight?
Yes. Skyler. I
was in a bar fight.
So you're okay?
Really?
Yes.
I'm okay.
And I think. in the end.
that it may have
been a good thing
because we were able to
clear the air and. you know...
Mutual respect. and...
So...
Frozen peas.
What?
It's the best thing
for the swelling.
Oh. it's not really
swollen. it's just...
No peas.
You don't even have ice.
I will get peas. I will get ice.
Peas and ice.
I'm writing it down.
I. um...
I need you to promise me
that if things do
get dangerous...
Skyler... Promise me.
Absolutely.
So...
Car wash.
[OVER SPEAKERS]  ♪
Trouble. kiss me again ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm hoping you are ♪
♪ Press it right there And
I'll pay you back double ♪
♪ But this ain't the real
thing Look at my lips ♪
WOMAN: Honey. Charles.
♪ Look at my teeth
They're just aching to bite ♪
Take a look at this kitchen.
♪ It's a big empty chasm ♪
Hi there. Can I
answer any questions?
Yes. Any chance of a top-off?
Oh. I think we can
help you out there.
♪ You've got compassion
Coming out of your ears ♪
So. what do you think?
Oh. very nice. Very open.
Oh. I agree. It flows. Mm.
Whole lot of natural light.
Michael Kilbourne.
Tori Costner. It's
nice to meet you.
Well. three bedrooms.
one and a half baths
on just under half an acre.
There's a non-attached
casita out in back.
Permit usable as
office or guest suite.
Hm. Plank wood floors.
Central heat and air.
I see you're married.
No. divorced.
Very recent.
Old habits. Oh. I'm sorry.
But any children?
Yes. as a matter
of fact. A little boy.
Oh. how old?
He turned 4 in May.
He's a Gemini.
Would love this yard.
Oh. plenty of space
for a jungle gym.
And the neighborhood
preschool is fantastic.
I think Eli is going
to be homeschooled.
Oh. well. great. Not
for religious reasons.
I wanna make sure
he's getting attention.
He'll still go to summer
camp and whatnot. playdates.
Don't want him to
be socially awkward.
Oh. no. Makes sense.
He tests very
highly. 96 percentile.
But that whole
right brain. left brain.
You want those in balance.
Oh. yeah.
You said the casita
has plumbing?
I work a lot with clay.
so I need access
to running water.
Well. it's pipe-fitted
for a quarter bath so...
Make a perfect studio.
Hm.
This could work.
Heh. heh. Hell.
that's the doctor's plan
to get her patients at ease.
If you know what I mean.
WOMAN 1: But. nurse...
MARIE: Hello? I'm back.
WOMAN 2: That's okay.
MARIE: Hank? Yeah.
[HANK CLEARS THROAT]
I had to go to three places
to get the moisturizer
that you like. But I got that.
And I got your Shiner
Bock and your chips.
And I couldn't resist.
The complete encyclopedia
to fantasy football.
Look. it has all
the latest rankings.
Marie. I said
Cheetos. not Fritos.
Wait. I...
I said Cheetos. like. 10 times.
You need me to write it down?
No. and I don't need you
to be mean about it either.
Well. I'm just saying. you know.
I said Cheetos.
"Ch." "ch." "ch" sound.
Virtually impossible to
confuse Cheetos with Fritos.
seems to me.
Where are you going?
I... Back to the store. I guess.
Here.
And the draft's not for two
months. so this is useless.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Can you believe it?
What?
What? This.
Well. you always said
this place could be bugged.
Now we know. Yeah. well.
I don't like it.
It's a violation of
the work space.
Yeah. I guess.
You wanna do something?
Do something?
Like what?
Go-karts?
Go-karts. What...?
Yeah. there's a track
down by the Coliseum.
It's pretty fun.
No. actually I have some
kind of a meeting. so...
All right. whatever.
Rain check?
Yeah. Sure.
How you doing?
Good. Yeah?
You okay?
Is there. uh. anything
we should talk about?
How's your eye?
Yeah. it's fine.
Anything we should talk about?
For what it's worth.
getting the shit
kicked out of you...
not to say you get used to it...
but you do kind
of get used to it.
Two words: nail salon.
Perfect for money laundering.
It's a high-volume business
with a discreet work force.
I mean. nobody does.
"Mister. me know nothing"
better than Mrs.
Mookjaiaporn and her gals.
Mr. Goodman...
"Saul." please.
Now. for the lady of the house.
Drum roll. How
about a lifetime supply
of French manicures
and enzyme peels?
Oh. yeah. go ahead.
Pinch yourself. Ha-ha-ha.
We're not buying a nail
salon. Mr. Goodman.
We're getting the car
wash. SAUL: I'm sorry.
Am I missing something
here? Didn't you already try that?
Yeah. I mean. Walt told me
that you took a run at
this Bogdan character
and he wrestled you into
submission with his eyebrows.
Ten million. that was
the asking price. right?
Apparently. he upped it to 20.
Wow. Nice negotiating.
Yeah. I mean. hey.
you bombed. It happens.
You were smart
to call me. Now...
You just sit back. relax. and
let a professional take over.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
That's for me. Excuse me.
What do you want?
I'm in a meeting.
Why didn't you think of
that before? It's not my...
I'm in a meeting.
Can Huell use your bathroom?
Huell?
Uh. sure. The top of the stairs.
He'll be quick.
It's a stomach thing. It's...
So where were we?
Professionalism. Yeah.
So if the guy won't
sell. he won't sell.
I don't accept that. I don't
accept that he won't sell.
I think he just
lacks the proper...
motivation.
Motivation. Ah.
As in "motivation" motivation?
I mean. just so we're
on the same page here.
are you saying we make
him an offer he can't refuse?
SKYLER: Nothing so
dramatic as that. no.
Motivation.
Attitude adjustment.
[LAUGHS]
This one. she's a keeper.
Well. an audit can
be highly motivating.
I know a gal at Tax and Revenue.
You give her 10 minutes.
she'll have his sky raining frogs.
No. we don't want to draw
any unwanted tax attention.
We don't want them looking
at us after Bogdan sells.
All right. how
about an ICE raid?
He's got illegals working
over there. He has to.
We are not getting a bunch
of poor. innocent
people in trouble. no.
Yeah. and also you're gonna
need them after you take over.
Hey. how about terrorism?
"Oh. Agent Hoover.
I gotta tell you.
"I've seen some real 'Islamic'
"comings and goings
over there at the car wash.
"Yeah. I mean. guys in turbans
pulling up in vans and
stuff like that." Ha. ha.
Saul. Bogdan is Romanian.
Okay. well. we're just
spitballing here. so...
Okay. there's always:
"You got a real nice place here.
Be a shame if something
happened to it." That angle.
What are you talking about?
Violence?
Attitude adjustment.
SKYLER: Oh. no. That. no.
That is not at all what I
meant. I... We do not do that.
That's not who we are. right?
Yeah. no. no. no. She's right.
Look. do I need to
state the obvious?
I mean. there's gotta be
dozens of car washes in this area.
Who says it has to be this one?
I do.
I say it has to.
Why?
I just do.
God.
Well. that clears things up.
I don't like him. Bogdan. Oh.
He was condescending to me.
rude about you.
and I do not like him.
Simple as that.
Hey. nobody appreciates
a passionate woman
more than I do.
But in this business...
And Walt can back me up on this.
The number one rule is
don't take things personally.
What do you mean. rude about me?
Something along the lines
of you weren't man enough
to face him yourself.
What?
SKYLER: That you
had to send your woman
to do your business for you.
[LAUGHS]
Okay. uh. speaking
as your lawyer.
I'm gonna go on record
and say this is a bad idea.
Now. I advise against...
It's this one. It's this one.
[SIGHS]
Okay. so. uh...
all we have to do is
think of a non-violent.
unsuspicious way to
purchase the car wash.
that protects the innocents
and doesn't cost $20 million.
Don't everybody speak at once.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
WOMAN: I like it. MAN: Mm-hm.
WOMAN: Yeah.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Hi.
Can I answer any questions?
Oh. Spoons.
Yes. the owner is
quite the collector.
Aren't they something?
One for each of the 50 states.
Puerto Rico is
technically a territory.
Huh.
You know. maybe they
were thinking. "Someday."
[LAUGHS]
So no basement?
No basement. Sorry.
That's a problem.
My brother's in the Peace Corps
and won't be back for 18 months
and I said I'd hang
on to his furniture.
Well. if you're looking
for storage space.
there's an attic area.
Oh. Well. an attic
might be even better.
as long as it's dry.
Let's take a tour. Okay.
Actually. I have
a handout for you.
It has all the information.
I'm Stephanie
Doswell. by the way.
Charlotte Blattner.
So nice to meet you.
Charlotte. You too.
So I told him point-blank.
You're my husband and I love
you. but you're 53 years old.
This job has just gotten
too stressful and difficult.
and it's time to quit.
And. miracle of
miracles. he listened.
What a fascinating career
that must have been for him.
It was.
I mean. NASA was like
a second family to us.
but. you know. it was
time for a new adventure.
So between his pension
and the income I bring
in from hand modeling.
we're. you know. comfortable.
When were these floors redone?
Two years ago. The
counters are brand-new.
I can tell. Travertine.
Nice.
Any children? No.
I don't really want kids.
Is that horrible for
me to say? Not at all.
Not everyone has
to have children.
You should talk to my
husband. [LAUGHS]
Garbage disposal?
[GARBAGE DISPOSAL WHIRRING]
[FEVER RAY'S "IF I
HAD A HEART" PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
♪ This will never end
'Cause I want more ♪
♪ More. give me
more Give me more ♪
♪ This will never end
'Cause I want more ♪
Check it out. Score. yo.
♪ Give me more ♪
MAN 1: Come on.
Come on. What you got?
MAN 2: You're going down!
[MAN 3 SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
♪ If I had a heart
I could love you ♪
♪ If I had a voice
I would sing ♪
♪ After the night
when I wake up ♪
[SCREAMING]
♪ I'll see what
Tomorrow brings ♪
♪ If I had a voice
I would sing ♪
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I really love your home.
Oh. well. thank you. Mimi.
It has a very European feel.
WOMAN: You think? Oh.
I lived in London for years.
so. yeah. this feels familiar.
Where in London? I was
stationed at Upwood in the '60s.
Downtown. but we
were almost never there.
My husband is an illustrator.
We traveled a lot.
Paris. Italy. Denmark.
It was before the
kids were in school.
so it was easy
to pick up and go.
That was before
my youngest. Lucy.
was diagnosed with endocarditis.
Oh. my. Gosh. is that...?
It's a bacterial infection
of the heart valves. It's...
Yeah. it can be...
WOMAN: Oh. that's terrible.
Is she all right?
Your daughter. Is she okay?
Yes. Thank you. Um...
The doctors put in
a prosthetic valve.
so she's... Lucy's fine.
Running and
walking. riding horses.
Thank goodness. MARIE: Yeah.
We're very lucky.
Excuse me. miss.
Very nice. thank you.
I just called the
police. Okay. then.
I know you stole that spoon.
What are you talking about?
You're a thief.
Excuse me? And a liar.
Making stories up.
What's wrong with you?
No. what's the matter with you?
You better just back off. okay?
My husband is a DEA agent.
Oh. I thought he
was an astronaut.
Or an illustrator. Get
your crazy lies straight.
You know what.
fatty? You are so lucky
that I am late for
an appointment.
You're not going anywhere.
MARIE: Let go of my purse!
Not until the police get here.
Let it go!
Let it go! Let it go!
You are in big trouble.
[RINGING]
Yeah.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Just slow... Hey. just...
Slow down. Start
from the... You're...
You're where?
Why the f...?
Why are you...?
Are you seriously
doing this to me again?
[SIGHS]
Jesus. just...
Would you stop crying?
I'll make a phone
call. Just sit tight.
Where they got you?
So good news. The officer
spoke to the homeowners.
They're not gonna press charges.
Good. I won't either.
Okay. then. So we're good to go.
You ready?
[SIGHS]
Marie. you wanna go home?
Marie?
[CRYING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Yes. it's Skyler White calling
for Saul Goodman. please.
Yes. it is important.
Thank you.
Sorry. Same as before.
But this is not right.
You cannot shut me
down. You cannot do this.
MAN: I've checked your
wastewater inside and out.
I've checked
your runoff gutters.
and now out here.
more contaminants.
Ammonia. acetone.
benzene. nitrobenzene.
BOGDAN: No. no.
no. this is a mistake.
Where is Gary? He'll tell you
my soap is very
good. very green.
Your soap is not the issue.
it's your filtration system.
The very least.
you'll need to retrofit.
But if you're leeching
into the groundwater.
which is a real
possibility here.
you're gonna need to
replace your system.
Replace?
Do you know what cost that is?
Two hundred thousand dollars.
It's a hardship.
If you like. we can give you
a list of approved vendors.
If you get going.
your downtime shouldn't
be any more than five weeks.
Okay. So sorry. you are right.
From now on. we will
be extra careful and clean.
No more pollution.
okay? Yes? No. I'm sorry.
The state requires you
to suspend all activity
until these levels reach
the mandated minimums.
Where is usual
man? Where is Gary?
Got transferred to Las Cruces.
If you'd like to
file an appeal...
I have done nothing wrong.
Tell me why you shut me down.
What laws did I break?
What laws? Several.
Tell me exact specific
laws or I refuse. Right now.
[STAMMERING]
Tell me what laws I
broke. The specific laws
SKYLER [ON EARPIECE]:
Hold on. Okay. hold on. hold on.
Wait. wait. wait. Okay.
Okay. The New Mexico
Hazardous Waste Act of 1978.
section 74. chapter
four. part 13 states:
"Whenever the disposal of solid
or hazardous waste presents"...
an imminent or
substantial endangerment.
the offender may be fined
not more than $5000 each
day in which the violation occurs.
All right. okay.
Now the...
Okay. baby.
All right. The EPA can cite him
under the Toxic Substances...
Control Act of 1976.
U.S. code. title
15. chapter 53...
"subchapter 1"...
section 2606.
Satisfied?
Was that specific...
specific enough for you?
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
MAN 1 [ON TV]: Threw
one in the channel in the 10th.
MAN 2: I guess they're
even now. MAN 1: Yep.
And they're even in
this match. Both have...
MARIE: All done with lunch? Hm.
You hardly touched this.
I'm not hungry.
Well...
I'm leaving the rice pudding.
I'm not hungry. Marie.
So don't eat it.
MAN 1: Speaking of babies.
he has a new one.
Joseph. and a son. Anthony.
[BEEPS]
[DISHWASHER WHIRRING]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hey. Marie. How you doing?
I'm okay. Is there a problem?
No. no. Everything's fine.
I'm here for Hank. actually.
Oh. you're so sweet.
Hank'll be thrilled.
MAN [ON TV]: Hard and straight.
And makes it the wrong
way. MARIE: Sweetie.
You have a visitor.
Oh. Jesus.
What now? She rob a bank?
Hey. buddy. How you doing?
Oh. well...
Can't complain. You know.
every day a little better.
ROBERTS: That's good.
You're looking good. Yeah. well.
handsome was
never the hard part.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Come on in. grab a seat.
Yeah. just throw
that stuff anywhere.
[SIGHS]
Listen. uh...
thanks again for the other day.
You know. this
whole thing. it's. uh...
It's been hard on her.
Forget it. Glad to help.
So rock collecting?
They're minerals. but. yeah.
It's cataloging. You know.
sort them. label them.
It's actually a
lot of work. Yeah.
No. it looks like it.
So. what's up?
Well.
actually. I could use
your help on something.
Homicide. Possibly drug-related.
You want my help on a case?
What am I. Ironside?
[CHUCKLING] No.
but you're a drug cop
who knows the local talent.
And you're a pal I
just did a favor for.
so let me pick your brain a sec.
You ever come across a guy
by the name of Gale Boetticher?
No.
Someone came along
and shot him in the face.
Okay. No signs of forced entry.
no signs of robbery.
Okay. so it's a
crime of passion.
Where's the drug angle?
We found a
notebook at his place.
I made a copy for you.
in case you're interested.
Looks like it
pertains to some kind
of methamphetamine superlab.
Yeah.
It's filled with
scientific formulas
and chemical purchase lists.
drawings. pages
and pages of this stuff.
It looks big-time.
but I'm no authority.
so I wonder if you
might take a look?
Come on. Tim. seriously?
What is this. some
sort of a charity thing?
Your expertise
could be useful here.
I'm lying here like third base.
living from bowel movement
to bowel movement.
I'm not even useful to myself.
Want my advice?
You take this to Steve Gomez.
He'll help you out. I
give this to Steve Gomez
and all of a sudden it
becomes a DEA case.
what good does that do me?
If you could just take a
look. tell me what I got here.
I'd really appreciate it.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Thanks. man.
Take it easy.
That's what I do.
[LAUGHS]
[TV TURNS ON]
[CROWD CHEERING ON TV]
MAN 1: No. no.
MAN 2: The three.
seven. nine. He says. "No."
[BABY COOING]
Well. it was a good try.
Here we go. Time
for your nap. Yeah.
Okay.
So...
Nail salon sounded
promising. What do you think?
I think we wait.
Wait?
Skyler. it has been five hours.
He'll call.
Just wait. Just wait.
Look...
It was a good idea. It was a
great idea. but it didn't work.
So why don't we simply
chalk it up as a learning...
[PHONE RINGING]
White residence.
Oh. hello. Mr. Wolynetz.
Am I still interested?
Well. I think that depends.
Yes. 879 was the original offer.
but that seems high to me now.
Now I'm offering
800. No. no. no.
No. don't do that. Why?
Well. because you're
an unpleasant
person. Mr. Wolynetz.
You were rude. disrespectful
towards my husband.
Furthermore. I've met with
quite a number of sellers
and the market seems much
softer than I thought. so 800.
[BOGDAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Uh-huh. Hm.
Well. I understand
that you're disappointed.
but that is my final offer.
I'm sorry we couldn't
make it work. Goodbye.
What are you doing?
I'm negotiating.
Why?
Because I want to pay less.
Oh. no.
Seventy-nine
thousand dollars less?
Who cares? Do you
know how much I make?
Yeah. but that's the very
reason we need to negotiate.
We don't wanna arouse suspicion
by not trying to
get a good deal.
Look. I get the logic. I do.
but you just went
too far with it.
You're calling him names?
I didn't call him names. I
said he was unpleasant.
[SIGHS]
Well. he's not calling you back.
I mean. you didn't
honestly think that worked?
Yeah. I do.
No way. Sorry. No.
So look. it's time to move on.
Okay? I'm gonna call Saul.
Where's my phone?
[PHONE RINGING]
No. What?
No. just... What for?
Wait. Wait.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Oh. my God.
Hello.
Hello. Mr. Wolynetz.
SKETCHY: No one's paying
attention to where these things are.
There's gotta be
thousands of them
all over the world
coming right for us.
And put one inside
an ice cream truck.
drive it into San Francisco.
I'm not even that scared of
burning up and cannibalism.
To me. the thing that
worries me is getting trampled
or shoved up against
a chain-link fence.
If you think about it. if you're
against a chain-link fence
and you've got a lot. I mean.
a lot of people
trying to escape.
pushing hard enough
forward. [GROANS]
you are gonna get squeezed
right through the chain links.
Like Play-Doh or
some kind of soft meat.
And this is inevitable. okay?
And there's nothing you or
me or anyone can do about it.
And if the fence
posts are stuck deep.
really deep with the cement.
way down inside the ground.
it's definitely
happening to you.
Oh. yeah. Yeah. bitch.
Somebody got shot.
Somebody probably got shot.
Like soft meat. man.
Right through. Squeezed
through there like soft meat.
Like soft meat.
Right through the chain links.
right through the chain links.
Hey. Hey.
[SNORING]
Money!
[ALL CLAMORING]
MAN 1: That one was mine.
MAN 2: Take it easy! MAN
3: Hey. you took mine. man!
WOMAN: Yeah!
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
SKYLER: Ooh.
Whoa.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Aww...
Nice. Yeah.
To clean cars and clean money.
Hear. hear.
You see?
I told you we'd get it.
Did you? Mm-hm.
Wow. Ha. ha.
Seriously.
It was really great work.
It's impressive.
Thank you.
And Saul finally
came through. Ahem.
Well. I mean. he
found the guy. right?
Well. yes. he found the guy.
but I told him what
to do and what to say.
You're right.
That's the hard part.
But. yes. Saul
was finally useful.
Ha. ha. Throw him a bone.
[LAUGHS]
Mm. Oh. my God.
This is truly amazing.
Yes. well. it better be.
Three hundred
twenty dollars a bottle.
What?
"Cuvée Pol Roger
Sir Winston Churchill."
Apparently. it was his
favorite champagne.
so they just named it after him.
How did you pay for
it? What do you mean?
Ah. No. Cash. I paid cash.
No. I'm asking how
did you. Walter White.
an unemployed
schoolteacher. pay for it?
How do you explain it? Skyler.
No one saw me.
Whoever sold it to you did.
And that's not the point.
The point is we're
broke. remember?
I'm waiting for your
unemployment check
so I can pay the phone bill.
I asked for an extension
from the power company. Why?
Because on paper.
we have no money.
You are completely overreacting.
I'm not apologizing for wanting
to celebrate in some small way.
I'm not asking you
to apologize. Walt.
I'm asking you to be smart.
I bought one bottle
of champagne.
One single bottle. Skyler.
I paid cash. That's it.
That's all it takes. okay? I
mean. look at Watergate.
One piece of duct tape on a door
brought down the president
of the United States.
What? I'm Nixon now? No.
What I'm saying is the
devil is in the details.
One little mistake.
one slipup in our story.
that could ruin us.
[SIGHS]
Fine.
Gotta destroy the evidence.
And when I look at this
image that is part of the record.
I am very concerned about
what sort of distraction
that could be.
whether it's from
any sort of signage.
but especially signage that's
changing every five seconds.
Thank you.
MAN: Any other questions?
We have a motion and
a second on the floor
to grant the appeal.
All those in favor. raise
your hand and say yes. Yes.
There's four in the
affirmative. Those opposed?
There's five no's and
the... That motion fails.
WOMAN: I would like to make
a motion to uphold the decision
and the findings of the EBC.
MAN: And the motion. then.
is seconded by Councilor Cook.
Any questions? I see none.
All those in favor.
signify by saying "yes"
to deny the appeal.
[INDISTINCT DIALOGUE ON TV]
All those in favor.
signify by saying "yes."
There's five in the affirmative.
All those opposed. say "no."
There's four in the
negative. Now. that passes.
[♪♪]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today